What makes you laugh the most?
是什么最能让你开怀大笑呢？
While rib-tickling jokes and hilarious videos certainly do make us giggle, most of the time we laugh because of something much simpler: being with other people.
虽然非常有趣的笑话和极其滑稽的视频确实会让我们咯咯地笑，但大多数时候，我们笑的原因要简单得多：和其他人在一起。
So much so that we are 30 times more likely to laugh when we're with others, according to a study by neuroscientist Robert Provine from the University of Maryland.
马里兰大学的神经科学家罗伯特·普罗文的一项研究表明，情况确实如此，当我们和别人在一起时，我们笑的可能性是独处时的30倍。
"When you're alone, laughter basically disappears," he told Smithsonian Magazine.
他在接受《史密森尼杂志》采访时说：“当你独自一人时，笑声基本上就消失了。”
So, what is it about other people that makes us split our sides?
那么，和其他人在一起时是什么让我们捧腹大笑呢？
The answer lies deep within our brains, and in how we form communities.
答案深藏在我们的大脑中，也在于我们如何形成社交群体。
Laughter is a social emotion that we use to "make and maintain social bonds," says Professor Sophie Smith from University College London in an article for the BBC.
伦敦大学学院的索菲·史密斯教授在为英国广播公司撰写的一篇文章中说，笑是一种社交情感，我们用它来“建立和维护社会联系”。
It reassures people that situations are non-threatening.
它让人们放心，情况并不具有威胁性。
Those who laugh frequently are also often more popular.
那些经常笑的人通常也更受欢迎。
Even in a normal conversation we laugh seven times every 10 minutes, she says.
她说，即使在正常的谈话中，我们每10分钟也会笑7次。
Professor Smith also explains that laughter is very different to speech.
史密斯教授还解释说，笑与说话完全不同。
It is non-verbal: the wheezing and snorting sounds are produced by air being pushed out quickly at high pressure, without involving the teeth or lips.
它是非语言的：喘息声和喷鼻声是由高压下快速排出的空气产生的，不涉及牙齿或嘴唇。
These sounds are the kind we make when in a state of heightened emotion.
这些声音是我们在情绪高涨时发出的那种声音。
In this respect, laughter sounds more like an animal call than human language.
从这个方面来看，笑声听起来更像是动物的叫声，而不是人类的语言。
This theory is backed up by tests which show the part of the brain responsible for laughter is not the neocortex used in language, but an 'older' area we share with mammals.
这一理论得到了测试的支持，测试表明，大脑中负责笑的部分不是用于语言的新皮质，而是我们与哺乳动物共有的一个“更古老”的区域。
Indeed, chimpanzees, gorillas and even rats all enjoy a good chortle, especially when being tickled.
确实，黑猩猩、大猩猩甚至老鼠都喜欢好好地咯咯笑，尤其是在被挠痒痒的时候。
Just be careful when you tickle a gorilla, or you might end up laughing on the other side of your face... (Did you laugh at that gag?
当你挠大猩猩痒痒的时候可要小心，否则你可能最终会转喜为忧……（你有没有被那个笑话逗笑呢？
Or did it just make you groan?)
还是它只是让你叹息？）